<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>

<title>Voicedrew's Microblog</title>
<link>https://voicedrew.xyz/</link>
<description>Actually an *average* sized blog</description>


<!-- LB -->

<item>
<title>    The Benevolant Tyrants</title>
<guid>https://voicedrew.xyz/microblog/The-Benevolant-Tyrants-6958.html</guid>
<link>https://voicedrew.xyz/microblog/The-Benevolant-Tyrants-6958.html</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:47:14 -0500</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[
    <h1>The Benevolant Tyrants</h1>
    <hr>
    <p>"Of all tyrannies a tyranny sincerely exercised for the good of its victims may be the most oppressive. It may be better to live under robber barons than under omnipotent moral busybodies. The robber baron's cruelty may sometimes sleep, his cupidity may at some point be satiated; but those who torment us for our own good will torment us without end for they do so with the approval of their own conscience." — C.S. Lewis</p>
    <small>Published on 2023-12-13 at 09:47:05</small>
]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>    Trolly Problem</title>
<guid>https://voicedrew.xyz/microblog/Trolly-Problem-8276.html</guid>
<link>https://voicedrew.xyz/microblog/Trolly-Problem-8276.html</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 11:38:31 -0500</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[
    <h1>Trolly Problem</h1>
    <hr>
    <p><img src="img/dilemma.png"></p>
    <small>Published on 2023-12-12 at 11:34:00</small>
]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>    Microblog</title>
<guid>https://voicedrew.xyz/microblog/Microblog-1741.html</guid>
<link>https://voicedrew.xyz/microblog/Microblog-1741.html</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:18:23 -0500</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[
    <h1>Microblog</h1>
    <hr>
    <p>So I spent most of the day setting up this microblogging system rather than studying. It works by creating a 2 temporary files, one for the title and another for the content of the post. It then opens neovim and allows me to edit the files. Once that is complete, the files are parsed, deleted, and then the page is generated. I use Luke Smith's sup script to update the RSS feed. <br><br>
I think I will keep this microblog as RSS exclusive, at least for the moment. The individual pages will always be available, of course.</p>
    <small>Published on 2023-12-11 at 17:18:17</small>
]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>    Progress</title>
<guid>https://voicedrew.xyz/microblog/Progress.html</guid>
<link>https://voicedrew.xyz/microblog/Progress.html</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 14:13:10 -0500</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[
    <h1>Progress</h1>
    <hr>
    <p>“We all want progress. But progress means getting nearer to the place where you want to be. And if you have taken a wrong turning then to go forward does not get you any nearer. If you are on the wrong road progress means doing an about-turn and walking back to the right road and in that case the man who turns back soonest is the most progressive man. There is nothing progressive about being pig-headed and refusing to admit a mistake. And I think if you look at the present state of the world it's pretty plain that humanity has been making some big mistake. We're on the wrong road. And if that is so we must go back. Going back is the quickest way on.” ― C.S. Lewis</p>
    <small>Published on 2023-12-11 at 13:32:05</small>
]]></description>
</item>

</channel>

</rss> 
