<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">

  <channel>
    <title>Your Feed Title</title>
    <link>http://www.yourwebsite.com</link>
    <description>Your feed description</description>
    <language>en-us</language>

    <!-- Add multiple items like this for each article or post -->
    <item>
      <title>Schizo-Ramblings About The Trolley Problem</title>
      <link>https://voicedrew.xyz/articles/trolley-problem.html</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
<h1 id="schizo-ramblings-about-the-trolley-problem">Schizo-Ramblings About The Trolley Problem</h1>
<h3 id="31-08-2023">31/08/2023</h3>
<p>EFAP, a podcast related to film, game, and critic criticism, recently had its 250th episode; it’s five-year anniversary. I’ve been a big fan of the show for years, so naturally, I tuned in.</p>
<p>On the show, they played <a href="https://neal.fun/absurd-trolley-problems/">Absurd Trolley Problems</a>... A game where one chooses either to pull or not pull the lever in an increasingly absurd set of trolley problems.</p>
<p>When they started playing the game, I found it extremely appalling that the cast almost unanimously agreed that diverting the train was the most moral action in the classic trolley problem. Here was my reasoning:</p>
<p>1) The train heading towards the 5 people is the state of nature.</p>
<p>2) By pulling, not pulling the lever, I am allowing them to die; not killing them.</p>
<p>3) Pulling the lever, and the subsequent death of the 1 person, is not the state of the world, but rather a consequence of my direct actions.</p>
<p>Here is the thought that put a monkey wrench into my reasoning: Is inaction an action? Or rather, ‘is it true that I am not killing anybody when I decide to do nothing?’ Here is the Oxford Dictionary definition of “inaction”</p>
<blockquote>
<p>“lack of action where some is expected or appropriate:”</p>
</blockquote>
<p>To further illustrate the problem, here is an absurd version of the trolley problem:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>"The trolley is headed towards one person. You can pull the lever to divert it to the other track, killing nobody instead. What do you do?"</p>
</blockquote>
<p>In this instance, would you not say that by allowing the train to continue in its path, you are killing the person on the tracks through your inaction?</p>
<h2 id="commission-vs-omission">Commission vs Omission</h2>
<p>I believe a key part of understanding the trolley problem is understanding the difference between crimes of commission, and crimes of omission. Crimes of commission constitute acts in which evil is caused as a consequence of malice, whereas crimes of omission are evils which are caused by a lack of action.</p>
<p>My error, then, was not recognizing crimes of omission as crimes at all.</p>
<h2 id="my-skin-in-the-game">My Skin In The Game</h2>
<p>Before coming to my previous realization, I believed that pulling the lever constituted a consequentialist action, whereas not pulling the lever was ontological. My ontological belief was essentially, “It is wrong to kill an innocent person, even if it’s a net positive”.</p>
<p>With the realization that allowing the 5 people to die <em>was</em> actually killing them due to omission, my view has changed on the trolley problem. I now believe ontology and consequentialism play a very mute role in this variation. Truly, if in both situations I am killing people, either by commission or omission, then indeed, the ontological belief that life is sacred, and that it should be preserved in the greatest numbers possible holds supreme.</p>
<hr>
<p>This post is a part of <a href="https://forum.agoraroad.com/index.php?threads/agora-road-travelouge-august-blogging.5966/">Agora Road's Travelouge</a>, an effort to promote blogging.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 22:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>

        <item>
      <title>Ramblings about web-design as escapism.</title>
      <link>https://walrus-island.neocities.org/navigation/blog</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
              <h1>
                Ramblings about web-design as escapism.
              </h1>
              <p>
                Most modern websites subscribe to the current paradigm of web design that tends to blend into one homogeneous sludge of clean cookie-cutter corporate minimalism with the same vibrancy and personality of a bowl of day old porridge. When everything starts looking the same, you start longing for, what i feel, was an integral part of the Web 2.0 period of the Wild West era of the internet. Variety and personality, each website being its own ecosystem of experimentation and expression, and with it came such a sense of exploration, of discovery and that, if you went deep enough through any website you would keep finding more secrets and parts of it unknown to you before!
              </p><p>
                For a while i settled into that feeling being part of a romanticized nostalgia of days gone. Which, while still partly true, changed when i stumbled upon the Personal Web due to a rabbit hole that began with wondering if Worlds.com was still alive and left me on the shores of the front page of the Yesterweb ( RIP in REST ), resulting in a sleepless night of euphoric exploration and discovery, each website it's own contained world, linked through with portals in the form of buttons and webrings to other digital lands, each distinct and full of charisma and things to do, read and explore. From minimal "small web" advocates, Web 1.0 philosophies and under construction prototypes to intricately designed virtual palaces of colors and bravado situated right next to Geocities homages and parodies alike and each so full of life in their own way, that feeling of discovery i attributed to nostalgia and romanticism surfaced back clear as ever, and it was beautiful. I still treasure the memory of that night and chuckle at the irony of it happening at the tail end of the Yesterweb life-span before it was told to keep looking at the flowers.
              </p>
              <p>
                I wish to argue then that that feeling of discovery and wonder is something that can be used to build your own internet space upon, something that when denizens want to explore and discover more of when they arrive. But also for yourself, turn it into the place you wish to escape to. I remember reading somewhere how one of the change in modern internet culture compared to that of our times was when the internet started being seen as more of a tool than an ecosystem, i agree with that sentiment wholeheartedly. And just with the wondrous ecosystems in nature, variety and uniqueness came, deserts, mountains, plains, oceans and in me personal case, an island.
              </p>
              <p>
                By making your website a place you yourself would stay to explore and dedicate time of your existence in, you help make these digital ecosystems flourish. I hope to bring me website to be the realm i envision it to, and will keep at it to bring that vision to be, of wonder, discovery, nature and style.
              </p>
              <p>
                Perhaps, as time goes by, someone else will also find a respite from the IRL in me far off island.
              </p>
              <p>
                This Walrus Island entry is part of the Agora Road's Travelogue.
              </p>

        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 21:30:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>

            <item>
      <title>Those of us who stayed, those of us who remain; Recounts from TFC.</title>
      <link>https://walrus-island.neocities.org/navigation/blog</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[

            <h1>
              Those of us who stayed, those of us who remain; Recounts from TFC.
            </h1>
            <p>
              I often find myself thinking about the kinds of games i play compared to the modern games that people are often fonding over and talking about constantly. Having had nothing but potato PC after toaster PC and me last owned console being the Playstation 2, the current hot gaming trend was out of the question for the longest time until more resent indie titles with more tuber friendly specs.
            </p>
            <p>
              So! We adapt as situations demands it, and ye follow for the next best thing when your device cant run Team Fortress 2. Which brings us to the quite specific example of Team Fortress Classic.
            </p>
            <p>
              A Half-Life mod from 1999 that appeared in the scene alongside Counter Strike, Ricochet and Deathmatch. The game had a lot of similarities to it's more popular sequel; red versus blue, the same 9 classes, maps with mirrored bases with intelligence to capture, capture points to name a few.
            </p>
            <p>
              It was a ditch effort in retrospective, who the bloody fuck would still be playing Team Fortress Classic? But, it was worth a shot for someone who was denied the spycrab hoovie extravaganza.
            </p>
            <p>
              No surprise to anyone, once booting up the game I was met with a sea of empty servers and the ruins of long abandoned game modes. But it wasnt all, there were a few populated even full servers. Those who stayed, those who remain.
            </p>
            <p>
              At first i did not think much of it, I was a kid who got what he wanted, a TF2 analog to play and enjoy. And enjoy i did, as it was and still is, pure clunky gold source chaos in its purest form. Rocket jumping, unbound bunny hopping from one point of the map to another in mere seconds, your body exploding from getting stabbed, your whole team getting infected by the enemy medic and dying of aids, and the ever so classic grenade mechanic that vanished when the jump to the sequel was made, of such variety from regular frag grenades to overpowered EMP, grenades that explodes into more grenades, others that rotates and shot nails and others that emanated hallucinatory spores! Pure, beautiful and delicious chaos accompanied with an equally chaotic in-game voice communication and chat. Some people might not like those things in their gaming experience, but I loved it from the mere second.
            </p>
            <p>
              Now, with a small player base, roughly around the less than 100 active players. You start seeing the same faces, you start to recognize players, playstyles, voices, quirks, and they start to recognize you as time goes on and you keep coming back. Something that it feels lost in the world of quick matching and censored chat lobbies with thousands of active players. You don't get to make friends with all of them, but you talk, and you hear about the glory days when a game barely anyone has heard of nowadays used to be as big as Half-Life Deathmatch and Counter Strike in its heyday, tournaments, mods, forums, LAN parties. All but fond memories for those who got to live through them, making a big chunk of those who stayed, those who remained because of nostalgia, attachment, and also common enough for preference. TF2 is a whole different game feel despite being the direct sequel, classes play different and the overall feeling is another as TFC is more chaotic and fast passed, we always get a reminded during the holiday steam sales when there is a slight spike in new players that come into one of the only remaining servers expecting to play it like TF2 only to get obliterated to the never return, fun times! Yet between them sometimes, very rarely, some stay.
            </p>
            <p>
              Originally i stayed out of necessity, after falling in love with the game, i stayed out of fondness and because of familiarity. As i said before, you get used to seeing the same people, you can feel their absence and it even impacts hard sometimes as it is always a reminder that we are playing on the eleventh hour of our games doomsday clock before it also becomes forever empty. Yet we remain, yet we stay, yet we play. It is nice to have an online place to return with people and faces you recognize, like a small-town bar where everyone knows your name even if you don't all get along.
            </p>
            <p>
              I feel like that is something we can most relate or long in our hidden corners of the web as we do our best to separate from the mainstram net. I know most feel that way about the road of whose community project this blogpost is a part of.
            </p>
            <p>
              We are the ones who stayed, we are the ones who remain.
            </p>
            <p>
              This Walrus Island entry is part of the Agora Road's Travelogue.
            </p>

        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 21:30:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Being a "Flip Phone Main"</title>
      <link>https://whitevhs.xyz/articles/2023/08/31/flip-phone-main</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
  <header>
<h1>Being a "Flip Phone Main"</h1>
  </header>
<hr>
<p style="color:white" class="meta">31 Aug 2023</p>
<div class="post">
<p>Around this time last year, my Samsung Galaxy S8 abruptly stopped working. Either it wouldn’t turn on or the display completely died. Regardless, I needed a quick and affordable replacement phone mainly for work. I really didn’t want another phone as I hardly used my last one but I didn’t have a choice when it came to work, so I settled on a $30 Alcatel flip phone. It runs an operating system called KaiOS, which apparently is a fork of the discontinued FirefoxOS, which is interesting. In this article, I’m gonna talk a bit about the pros and cons of daily driving a flip phone.</p>

<h2 id="the-pros">The Pros</h2>
<p>Your phone is no longer a potential source of distraction - it is merely a tool for communication or time management. I didn’t spend much time on my phone to begin with, but this really cut it down to only when I needed it, no more and no less. The form factor is quite nice as well, I like the smaller fit of the phone in the hand, and the crisp clap of closing the phone is very satisfying. Having actual tactile buttons on the phone feels nice, though I would prefer to have a “sliding phone” with a full keyboard. The battery life on it is great, which makes sense considering I only use it a few minutes each day. I can go 4-5 days without charging it sometimes, and it’s fully charged within a couple of hours. My phone plan is only $15 a month which is very affordable.</p>

<h2 id="the-cons">The Cons</h2>
<p>Technologies like SMS/MMS and voice calls over a cellular network are terrible for privacy, as all of the information being transmitted is unencrypted, and is even sold to data brokers and government agencies to spy on you. When you do actually use the phone to send messages, typing on it can be a pain. The predictive text is awful so I disabled it. I can get quick messages across in a snap, but anything of length instantly becomes a chore. With the model of phone I have, there is no option to block numbers, so if there’s a number that keeps harassing me, I’m basically screwed. The phone needs to be restarted frequently, as the OS becomes slow and very unresponsive over time.</p>

<h2 id="the-conclusion">The Conclusion</h2>
<p>If you’re the kind of person who only uses calls/text sparingly and doesn’t need a constant distraction in their pocket, then consider switching to a flip phone (or more generally a “dumb phone”). If your use case doesn’t quite line up with the limitations, consider using an Android device with a debloated ROM on it, and only use the necessary apps.</p>
<p>-H</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 20:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Personal Websites</title>
      <link>https://whitevhs.xyz/articles/2023/08/29/personal-websites</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[

  <header>
<h1>The Importance of Personal Websites</h1>
  </header>
<hr>
<p style="color:white" class="meta">29 Aug 2023</p>
<div class="post">
<p>My site has been up for just over a year now, and in that time I’ve encountered so many interesting websites, all of them respectively created and maintained by just one person in their free time. Most of them share the same sentiment that having a personal website is liberating, and can be a great way of getting your thoughts and ideas out. Having a place to properly and freely express yourself is critical. Most Big Tech platforms can and will ban whoever they feel like without a moment’s notice, and without reason. After all, it’s in their <a href="https://tosdr.org">Terms of Service</a>. Most of them also require you to use your real identity. You should have the choice to remain anonymous online. While I do believe more people should have their own website, at the same time I understand that it’s not for everyone. If you want to carve out your own space online that you can <em>truly</em> call home, consider creating your own website(s). But before you do, you might ask yourself:</p>

<h2 id="where-do-i-start">Where do I start?</h2>
<p>This is a great question, but the answer will be different for everyone, as it really depends on what you want to do with your site. I highly recommend checking out <a href="https://forum.agoraroad.com/index.php?threads/the-personal-web.5647/">this thread</a> on Agora Road; it’s what prompted me to write this in the first place. Included in the thread is a list of ways you can start working on your site, which I implore you to peruse through if you’re truly interested in creating your own site. In this post I’m gonna break down my workflow for this site.</p>

<h2 id="the-cost">The cost</h2>
<p>When I first became interested in hosting my own website, I wanted to do so in a way that would cost me the least amount of shekels. I purchased my domain on <a href="https://epik.com/">Epik</a> for about two dollars. Renewing it does cost more, however (I think it was like $35 to renew it til 2025). Keep in mind, some of the ways you can go about creating your site will NOT require a custom domain, it’s more of an optional thing. Anyway, I remember stumbling on a website hosted with Github Pages. Looking into it, I found out that you can easily host a website on there for free. That led me down the path of using a Static Site Generator (or SSG). By default Github Pages uses the Jekyll SSG so that’s what I went with. Eventually <a href="https://nogithub.codeberg.page/">I migrated all of my code to Gitlab</a> because I’d rather not use a Microsoft owned service. I’ll admit, having very little experience with this sort of thing meant that my first month had a somewhat steep learning curve, with lots of trial and error. I wanted to do everything by hand, and figuring out how to set everything up was confusing at first, for sure. But the more time I took to figure it out, the more I actually understood what I was doing. Sidenote: I still have no idea what I’m doing.</p>

<h2 id="the-code">The code</h2>
<p>Using an SSG means the actual pipeline for your site is handled for you (of course you have to configure it initially, but it’s a “set it and forget it” kinda thing). You make your changes, commit it, and boom, within a couple minutes your changes are live. Before I realized I can just press F12, edit the HTML or CSS on the site locally, then apply those changes to the actual codebase, I was making the smallest little changes and committing them. DO NOT MAKE THE SAME MISTAKE AS ME. I feel stupid for not realizing it sooner, but the cleaner you can keep your commits, the better. Using an SSG means you can set up layouts for your page, which is handy for not having to include a bunch of redundant code in your index.html files. For example, everything at the top and bottom of my site is included in the layout (header + footer), and all the actual content of the page is injected via liquid tags.</p>

<h2 id="the-possibilities">The possibilities</h2>
<p>The best part about owning your own site, in my opinion, is just the sheer amount of possibilities there are. The biggest limitations you have are your imagination and ability to produce the necessary code. You can turn it into anything you’d like. In all honesty, you don’t <em>have</em> to write all the code by hand. There are tons of templates and themes out there available for public use, however I personally did not take that route as I wanted to learn how to do it from scratch. Take whatever path you feel is the best for you.</p>

<h2 id="the-downsides">The downsides</h2>
<p>Of course, the method I chose for hosting my site does have its downsides. One of them being the fact that I’m not self-hosting, and technically I am still at the mercy of Gitlab if they so choose to terminate my account. This does pose a potential problem if the kind of content you want to display on your site goes against their terms. Another downside is the fact it is only a static site, and you don’t have any access to tools like PHP for backend stuff. You’re basically stuck with the limitations that are imposed on you. But hey, it’s gratis (free as in “free beer”) and so far I’ve managed just fine. Again, it all comes down to what you’d like to do with your website.</p>

<p>The importance of these independent spaces online cannot be overstated. They’re essential for a free and open web. It gives me hope to see that this “Old Web Revival” movement exists to some degree. If you are curious about the personal websites that are out there, check out the <a href="https://wiby.me/">Wiby search engine</a>, or search out the various <a href="https://wikiless.org/wiki/Webring">Webrings</a> that exist. Have fun creating and exploring.</p>

<p>-H</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 20:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Burden of Life birthed by Lamenting Death.</title>
      <link>https://risingthumb.xyz/Writing/Articles/The_Burden_of_Life_birthed_by_Lamenting_Death</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
<h1>The Burden of Life birthed by Lamenting Death.
</h1>
<p>
</p>
<h2>Lament
</h2>
<p>
</p>
<p>Oh my dear Brothers, that we shall die is to live. But whether we live life, or life lives us- or that we live death, and die to life... death is only an end, of our means.
</p>
<p>
</p>
<p>Memento Mori, the old saying of Latin. Remember you will die. When your death weighs upon you, as it upon the Camel of Zarathustra's 1st metamorphosis, you stray and steer. You search for comforts to this end. And the end of this, is a discomfort, the denial of life.
</p>
<p>
</p>
<p>How is it a denial of life? There are first those who ascribe negative value to life. Who preach antinatalism. They deny pleasures of the flesh- sex and reproduction is one pleasure, the creation and raising of a child is another pleasure. Creation, a primal pleasure- as in God's Genesis, in our regenesis. We cry, and wiggle- we decry and sizzle in the boiling hot coals of life's suffering.
</p>
<p>
</p>
<p>Life is suffering. And to suffer, is to live my friends.
</p>
<p>
</p>
<p>It is some comfort to say at the end, there is a shining beacon found in the afterlife. In Valhalla for the virtuous warrior. In Heaven for the virtuous imitator of Christ, graced by Christ. All of these are a denial of life, by an affirmation of the afterlife. An affirmation beyond the veil of death. That there is no basis to believe or disbelieve- that Pascal in the self-same wager that affirms and slays his God as believer, has condemned to the herds of other idols. That God competes in the abyss of all other Gods, even those to whom Goodness is Evil to Christians.
</p>
<p>
</p>
<p>Oh friends, the bells toll each hour. One toll to your booth, the repentance of your sins. Oh God! I cannot see any more graves! I cannot see people pay in life, for their death. Show me something good, something joyous.
</p>
<p>
</p>
<p>That deaths is an end, the idleness of our bodies. The eternal Sunday. God rested. We rested. And we never wake. It is the end of a week's creation. The end of a life's creation. Our children, our family, our friends weep. All our creation... and all creation wept.
</p>
<p>
</p>
<p>It is a lament, that death is the primal fear, the basis of denial in our life- so struck dumb with stress, terror, nightmares of the night's mares that come to reap what was sown.
</p>
<p>
</p>
<h2>Burden
</h2>
<p>
</p>
<p>That we create our vision of death, is a creation of the burdens. Of the Camel. Of the desire to hold all our responsibility and life upon our back- and in such a simple creation, we weep, lament, and are crushed under them. Unlike Sisyphus, we take no joy in the boulder of life- and deny it. Is there an object to it? Or is it a phantasm of the mind? That haunts our every step with the sickly black tar that coats and crushes everything deep to the depth- that the Camel may bear no more. Painted black.
</p>
<p>
</p>
<p>I see my burdens painted black, and see no light at the end. That there is death is a corrosion to all Good, all Evil and all Creation. Death is entropy, an ends, and our wills and woulds are a means to this ends- baked, burnt or bastardised.
</p>
<p>
</p>
<p>All philosophy comes down to the question. Why live? As Camus said "the only philosophical question of any significance is the question of suicide". That we live in an absurdity, that we take our burdens in both hands, and roll it up the hill- knowing Gravity, knowing Entropy, knowing the world is a mocking jester at every turn.
</p>
<p>
</p>
<p>But even the heavy jester creates joy out of the decks of tragedy, cards of comedy... birth of a dancing star. With such burdens, they can leap with joy and light-footed and heavy with life and vitality.
</p>
<p>
</p>
<p>Steer clear of these preachers of death, and find bridges to the Übermensch my Brothers. That your lives might be your virtue, and your highest hope kept holy. Memento Mori. Your highest hope is the creation of your second life. The life beyond your death. The creation beyond your life. What passes down your legacy and life, your tribe and world. Seven generations of thick skin have begotten you, and you are their highest hope kept holy- will you defile it in death, or honour in holy life?
</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 20:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>

        <item>
      <title>God Does Not Accept Second Rate Sacrifices</title>
      <link>https://voicedrew.xyz/articles/try-your-hardest.html</link>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[

<h1 id="god-does-not-accept-second-rate-sacrifices">God Does Not Accept Second Rate Sacrifices</h1>
<h3 id="18-06-2023">18/06/2023</h3>
<p>This blog post originally started its life as an account of my last year of school, and how because I did not try my best, I got a second rate reward for my minimal efforts. As a began to wrap up that post with a conclusion, I noticed that I was directly contradicting my thesis. Even though I had failed to get into a specific university program, I had also grown tremendously over the year, and so I had nothing to be ashamed about. It is from the ashes of that post that I write this one.</p>
<p>I propose that you fully commit to what matters to you, since it's much more rewarding to receive full compensation for your complete efforts than to receive no reward, or even punishment, for putting in not enough effort. God, after all, does not accept second-rate sacrifices.</p>
<p>I’ve recently started going to the gym again. I had been going previously in the year, but I fell off hard around the time school ended. I ended up losing a lot of my muscle, and my body fat shot up; my level of exercise had changed, but my diet had not.</p>
<p>Before I stopped, I had been going 3 times a week, working the same muscles every time. Biceps, Triceps, Shoulders, and Chest. My diet was almost completely carbohydrates, and not particularly conducive to muscle growth. I did see changes in my body, but they were not fast, nor particularly impressive. It is no wonder then that I stopped. I was not particularly invested in fitness, because I was hardly seeing any of the benefits of that lifestyle.</p>
<p>I am doing things completely differently this time around. I am putting in the work and making the necessary sacrifices that someone who <em>deserves</em> to have a nice body would make. I cook simple, wholesome, protein rich meals for myself. I’m in the gym 6 days a week, running a push pull legs split. I try to train the same muscles with different, more interesting lifts, such that I won't simply fall into a routine and get bored. I do drop sets to get every last bit of growth I can out of my time.</p>
<p>It has only been like two weeks, and I can already say, I’m super impressed. I managed to get to the same bench press that took me 4 months previously in an eighth the time. There is none of that dread that I used to feel as a consequence of going three days a week. Now, it is simply a thing I do every day at a specific time, making it very hard to justify skipping workouts. The ends, now, justify the means.</p>
<p>Few regret failure after an honest effort, but all regret not trying enough and getting exactly what they deserve. </p>
<hr>
<p>This post is a part of <a href="https://forum.agoraroad.com/index.php?threads/agora-road-travelouge-august-blogging.5966/">Agora Road's Travelouge</a>, an effort to promote blogging.</p>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 20:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>

  </channel>

</rss>
